[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House Speaker"], "LOCATION": ["Wolf"], "PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What is the very latest, Dana?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "very", "latest", ",", "Dana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "The very latest, Wolf, is I'm actually standing here, John Boehner, the House Speaker's office is back there, one of his top lieutenants just came out and said there is no deal, no deal.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "very", "latest", ",", "Wolf", ",", "is", "I", "'m", "actually", "standing", "here", ",", "John", "Boehner", ",", "the", "House", "Speaker", "'s", "office", "is", "back", "there", ",", "one", "of", "his", "top", "lieutenants", "just", "came", "out", "and", "said", "there", "is", "no", "deal", ",", "no", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Is that fair?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "fair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "It could be if he's in the place where he can offer something.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "be", "if", "he", "'s", "in", "the", "place", "where", "he", "can", "offer", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What are you hearing from your sources, Dan?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "from", "your", "sources", ",", "Dan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, Wolf, lately, in the last few hours or so, things have been very quiet here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Wolf", ",", "lately", ",", "in", "the", "last", "few", "hours", "or", "so", ",", "things", "have", "been", "very", "quiet", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Either way, no matter what happens, is it fair to say that we will definitely hear from the president of the United States tonight, Dan, before this midnight deadline?", "question_tokens": ["Either", "way", ",", "no", "matter", "what", "happens", ",", "is", "it", "fair", "to", "say", "that", "we", "will", "definitely", "hear", "from", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "tonight", ",", "Dan", ",", "before", "this", "midnight", "deadline", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Wolf, the indication we were getting was that the president -- there was a good chance the president would come out and say something tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["Wolf", ",", "the", "indication", "we", "were", "getting", "was", "that", "the", "president", "--", "there", "was", "a", "good", "chance", "the", "president", "would", "come", "out", "and", "say", "something", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"], "LOCATION": ["United States"], "TIME": ["this midnight"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "So, how is that even possible that there could be a shutdown?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "how", "is", "that", "even", "possible", "that", "there", "could", "be", "a", "shutdown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, that's an excellent point on the last point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "excellent", "point", "on", "the", "last", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Is the issue right now -- based on everything you know, Congresswoman -- the money, the amount of cuts that are proposed in this budget, or is it some of the social issues like funding for Planned Parenthood?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "issue", "right", "now", "--", "based", "on", "everything", "you", "know", ",", "Congresswoman", "--", "the", "money", ",", "the", "amount", "of", "cuts", "that", "are", "proposed", "in", "this", "budget", ",", "or", "is", "it", "some", "of", "the", "social", "issues", "like", "funding", "for", "Planned", "Parenthood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ":", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, this isn't anything new, Wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "n't", "anything", "new", ",", "Wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner", "Harry Reid"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Well, what's the sticking point right now, based on what you know?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "sticking", "point", "right", "now", ",", "based", "on", "what", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, again, we don't know because the negotiations are only being handled by John Boehner, the vice president, the president and Harry Reid.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "because", "the", "negotiations", "are", "only", "being", "handled", "by", "John", "Boehner", ",", "the", "vice", "president", ",", "the", "president", "and", "Harry", "Reid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Are you telling me that the speaker isn't consulting with key members, like you, especially given your influence among those who support the Tea Party movement?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "telling", "me", "that", "the", "speaker", "is", "n't", "consulting", "with", "key", "members", ",", "like", "you", ",", "especially", "given", "your", "influence", "among", "those", "who", "support", "the", "Tea", "Party", "movement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "The speaker needs to be able to do his negotiations.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "speaker", "needs", "to", "be", "able", "to", "do", "his", "negotiations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Can we assume, Congresswoman, that whatever the speaker of the House, John Boehner, agrees to will be good enough for your vote?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "assume", ",", "Congresswoman", ",", "that", "whatever", "the", "speaker", "of", "the", "House", ",", "John", "Boehner", ",", "agrees", "to", "will", "be", "good", "enough", "for", "your", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, what -- no, what I have said from the beginning is I can't vote for any deal that doesn't defund Obamacare.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "--", "no", ",", "what", "I", "have", "said", "from", "the", "beginning", "is", "I", "ca", "n't", "vote", "for", "any", "deal", "that", "does", "n't", "defund", "Obamacare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congresswoman", "House"], "PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "So, you're -- are you speaking -- excuse me for interrupting -- but are you speaking, you think, for the vast majority of those Tea Party activists in the House of Representatives?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "'re", "--", "are", "you", "speaking", "--", "excuse", "me", "for", "interrupting", "--", "but", "are", "you", "speaking", ",", "you", "think", ",", "for", "the", "vast", "majority", "of", "those", "Tea", "Party", "activists", "in", "the", "House", "of", "Representatives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ":", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "House of Representatives"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", ",", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Do you agree with a lot of conservative Republicans, including Karl Rove, and Mike Huckabee, that there's got to be a deal that averts a government shutdown, otherwise this could be a political disaster for Republicans right now, just as the shutdown back in '95 turned out to be a political disaster for the Republicans then?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "a", "lot", "of", "conservative", "Republicans", ",", "including", "Karl", "Rove", ",", "and", "Mike", "Huckabee", ",", "that", "there", "'s", "got", "to", "be", "a", "deal", "that", "averts", "a", "government", "shutdown", ",", "otherwise", "this", "could", "be", "a", "political", "disaster", "for", "Republicans", "right", "now", ",", "just", "as", "the", "shutdown", "back", "in", "'95", "turned", "out", "to", "be", "a", "political", "disaster", "for", "the", "Republicans", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNPS", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "I think people all over the country have been telling us fight, keep fighting.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "all", "over", "the", "country", "have", "been", "telling", "us", "fight", ",", "keep", "fighting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karl Rove", "Mike Huckabee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"], "PERSON": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Quick question before I let you go, are you in the Republican presidential contest?", "question_tokens": ["Quick", "question", "before", "I", "let", "you", "go", ",", "are", "you", "in", "the", "Republican", "presidential", "contest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, Wolf, we'll make a decision probably sometime early this summer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Wolf", ",", "we", "'ll", "make", "a", "decision", "probably", "sometime", "early", "this", "summer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "How worried wore you about challenging Donald Trump for the party's nomination?", "question_tokens": ["How", "worried", "wore", "you", "about", "challenging", "Donald", "Trump", "for", "the", "party", "'s", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Oh, I'm not worried at all, because, again, I think that the contest is only early on and starting.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "worried", "at", "all", ",", "because", ",", "again", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "contest", "is", "only", "early", "on", "and", "starting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["June"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How does this sound to you, Trump-Bachmann or Bachmann- Trump, how does that ticket sound to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "this", "sound", "to", "you", ",", "Trump-Bachmann", "or", "Bachmann-", "Trump", ",", "how", "does", "that", "ticket", "sound", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, we'll let you know in early June.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'ll", "let", "you", "know", "in", "early", "June", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trump"], "PERSON": ["Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What's the latest guidance you're getting about deal or no deal?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "latest", "guidance", "you", "'re", "getting", "about", "deal", "or", "no", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, I'm getting that everybody understands -- at least the leaders understand that they need to get a deal, that the American public wants a deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "getting", "that", "everybody", "understands", "--", "at", "least", "the", "leaders", "understand", "that", "they", "need", "to", "get", "a", "deal", ",", "that", "the", "American", "public", "wants", "a", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What's your understanding?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "understanding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, I'm thinking it would be what I would be called a comprehensive deal that would come in more than one part.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "thinking", "it", "would", "be", "what", "I", "would", "be", "called", "a", "comprehensive", "deal", "that", "would", "come", "in", "more", "than", "one", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "This continuing -- this resolution, this budget will continue to fund the health care law, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "continuing", "--", "this", "resolution", ",", "this", "budget", "will", "continue", "to", "fund", "the", "health", "care", "law", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBG", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "LYBURN: Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["LYBURN", ":", "Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Planned Parenthood"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What about funding for -- what about funding for Planned Parenthood?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "funding", "for", "--", "what", "about", "funding", "for", "Planned", "Parenthood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ":", "WP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Well, remember, Planned Parenthood is a small part of what we call Title X funding.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "remember", ",", "Planned", "Parenthood", "is", "a", "small", "part", "of", "what", "we", "call", "Title", "X", "funding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Has it always been a sensitive issue or is this an unusually -- an unusual moment for Planned Parenthood based on your history right now?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "it", "always", "been", "a", "sensitive", "issue", "or", "is", "this", "an", "unusually", "--", "an", "unusual", "moment", "for", "Planned", "Parenthood", "based", "on", "your", "history", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well, Wolf, I've never seen anything like it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Wolf", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "seen", "anything", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Well, the way I would put it is we're actually the largest family planning provider in the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "way", "I", "would", "put", "it", "is", "we", "'re", "actually", "the", "largest", "family", "planning", "provider", "in", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Is Planned Parenthood -- your critics make this point and they have advertisements that make this point -- the largest abortion provider in the United States?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Planned", "Parenthood", "--", "your", "critics", "make", "this", "point", "and", "they", "have", "advertisements", "that", "make", "this", "point", "--", "the", "largest", "abortion", "provider", "in", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", ":", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I -- here's what I do know: we're the largest family planning provider in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "here", "'s", "what", "I", "do", "know", ":", "we", "'re", "the", "largest", "family", "planning", "provider", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Is it the largest abortion provider, too?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "the", "largest", "abortion", "provider", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "And I think one thing that is really, really -- I haven't counted, you know, what services every health care provider provides in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "one", "thing", "that", "is", "really", ",", "really", "--", "I", "have", "n't", "counted", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "services", "every", "health", "care", "provider", "provides", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What are you hearing over there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "hearing", "over", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I think first we should make clear that operations in Afghanistan aren't going to be affected, because they're funded by a part of the budget kind of immune to this shutdown.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "first", "we", "should", "make", "clear", "that", "operations", "in", "Afghanistan", "are", "n't", "going", "to", "be", "affected", ",", "because", "they", "'re", "funded", "by", "a", "part", "of", "the", "budget", "kind", "of", "immune", "to", "this", "shutdown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "In terms of morale, in terms of fighting spirit, are you getting any indication at all that this debate that's under way in Washington is impacting the ability of the U.S. military to do their jobs on the battlefield?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "morale", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "fighting", "spirit", ",", "are", "you", "getting", "any", "indication", "at", "all", "that", "this", "debate", "that", "'s", "under", "way", "in", "Washington", "is", "impacting", "the", "ability", "of", "the", "U.S.", "military", "to", "do", "their", "jobs", "on", "the", "battlefield", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "It's very early days.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "early", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "You don't have a whole lot of money in the bank, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "whole", "lot", "of", "money", "in", "the", "bank", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "How much money, if I may ask, do you have in the bank?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "money", ",", "if", "I", "may", "ask", ",", "do", "you", "have", "in", "the", "bank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Right now, I just put my husband's truck up for sale.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "I", "just", "put", "my", "husband", "'s", "truck", "up", "for", "sale", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "You would be in deep trouble if that paycheck stopped even for a week?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "be", "in", "deep", "trouble", "if", "that", "paycheck", "stopped", "even", "for", "a", "week", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Even for a week, yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Even", "for", "a", "week", ",", "yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "So how scared are you right now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "scared", "are", "you", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I'm very frightened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "frightened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Have you had a chance to talk at all about this with your son?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "a", "chance", "to", "talk", "at", "all", "about", "this", "with", "your", "son", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "My son knows a little bit about what's going on.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "son", "knows", "a", "little", "bit", "about", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "David, what do you think about that?", "question_tokens": ["David", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Look, I'm disgusted with both sides.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'m", "disgusted", "with", "both", "sides", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Do you agree, Ashwin, that from time to time, and probably right now, the fighting men and women of the United States, the U.S. military personnel are merely some sort of poker chips, if you will, being used by both political parties?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", ",", "Ashwin", ",", "that", "from", "time", "to", "time", ",", "and", "probably", "right", "now", ",", "the", "fighting", "men", "and", "women", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "the", "U.S.", "military", "personnel", "are", "merely", "some", "sort", "of", "poker", "chips", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "being", "used", "by", "both", "political", "parties", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, I hope that's not true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "that", "'s", "not", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashwin"], "LOCATION": ["United States", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I'm one of those people that are outraged by it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "one", "of", "those", "people", "that", "are", "outraged", "by", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Is that what you're hearing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Is this a significant split or is it overblown?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "significant", "split", "or", "is", "it", "overblown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "No, I don't think there's a split.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "split", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "You believe, based on the experience that you as a Republican leader had in '95 during the last government shutdown -- you want a deal right now, under any circumstances, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "believe", ",", "based", "on", "the", "experience", "that", "you", "as", "a", "Republican", "leader", "had", "in", "'95", "during", "the", "last", "government", "shutdown", "--", "you", "want", "a", "deal", "right", "now", ",", "under", "any", "circumstances", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "No, that's not right at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "right", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "Tea Party"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ":", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What's a deal breaker for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "a", "deal", "breaker", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Well, the fact of the matter is we have a Congress -- and today I work with grassroots activists known as the Tea Party movement.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "fact", "of", "the", "matter", "is", "we", "have", "a", "Congress", "--", "and", "today", "I", "work", "with", "grassroots", "activists", "known", "as", "the", "Tea", "Party", "movement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Are you going to vote for this deal tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "vote", "for", "this", "deal", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I don't know what the deal is, Wolf.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "the", "deal", "is", ",", "Wolf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Is that what you're saying, congressman?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", ",", "congressman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "What I'm saying is I'll consider reasonable proposals.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "'m", "saying", "is", "I", "'ll", "consider", "reasonable", "proposals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]